// letters used for levels 1-3
const letters = {
  upperLetters: 'ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ',
  lowerLetters: 'abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz',
  mixLetters: 'ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZabcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz',
};

// special characters used for level 7
const specialChars = ',.!@#$%^&*()"<>[]-=+_?\';:';

// short animal words used in level 4
const shortAnimals = [
  { problem: '🐄', answer: 'cow' },
  { problem: '🐈', answer: 'cat' },
  { problem: '🐕', answer: 'dog' },
  { problem: '🐅', answer: 'tiger' },
  { problem: '🐎', answer: 'horse' },
  { problem: '🐖', answer: 'pig' },
  { problem: '🐁', answer: 'mouse' },
  { problem: '🦆', answer: 'duck' },
  { problem: '🦉', answer: 'owl' },
  { problem: '🐸', answer: 'frog' },
  { problem: '🐍', answer: 'snake' },
  { problem: '🦈', answer: 'shark' },
  { problem: '🐌', answer: 'snail' },
  { problem: '🕷️', answer: 'spider' },
  { problem: '🐝', answer: 'bee' },
  { problem: '🦥', answer: 'sloth' },
  { problem: '🦨', answer: 'skunk' },
  { problem: '🐻', answer: 'bear' },
  { problem: '🦁', answer: 'lion' },
  { problem: '🦊', answer: 'fox' },
  { problem: '🐺', answer: 'wolf' },
  { problem: '🐰', answer: 'rabbit' },
  { problem: '🐠', answer: 'fish' },
  { problem: '🐳', answer: 'whale' },
  { problem: '🦈', answer: 'shark' },
  { problem: '🐢', answer: 'turtle' },
  { problem: '🐑', answer: 'sheep' },
  { problem: '🐐', answer: 'goat' },
  { problem: '🦌', answer: 'deer' },
  { problem: '🦅', answer: 'eagle' },
  { problem: '🐜', answer: 'ant' },
  { problem: '🦇', answer: 'bat' },
];

const bodyParts = [
  { problem: '🖐️', answer: 'hand' },
  { problem: '👊', answer: 'fist' },
  { problem: '🦵', answer: 'leg' },
  { problem: '🦶', answer: 'foot' },
  { problem: '💪', answer: 'arm' },
  { problem: '👂', answer: 'ear' },
  { problem: '👃', answer: 'nose' },
  { problem: '🧠', answer: 'brain' },
  { problem: '👀', answer: 'eyes' },
  { problem: '👁️', answer: 'eye' },
  { problem: '🦷', answer: 'tooth' },
  { problem: '🦴', answer: 'bone' },
  { problem: '👄', answer: 'mouth' },
  { problem: '👅', answer: 'tongue' },
  { problem: '👣', answer: 'feet' },
  { problem: '🩸', answer: 'blood' },
  { problem: '🤲', answer: 'hands' },
  { problem: '👶', answer: 'baby' },
  { problem: '🧍‍♂️', answer: 'man' },
  { problem: '🧍‍♀️', answer: 'woman' },
  { problem: '👍', answer: 'thumb' },
];

const colors = [
  { problem: '🟥', answer: 'red' },
  { problem: '🔴', answer: 'red' },
  { problem: '🔺', answer: 'red' },
  { problem: '⬜', answer: 'white' },
  { problem: '⚪', answer: 'white' },
  { problem: '⬛', answer: 'black' },
  { problem: '⚫', answer: 'black' },
  { problem: '🟦', answer: 'blue' },
  { problem: '🔵', answer: 'blue' },
  { problem: '🔷', answer: 'blue' },
  { problem: '🟫', answer: 'brown' },
  { problem: '🟤', answer: 'brown' },
  { problem: '🟩', answer: 'green' },
  { problem: '🟢', answer: 'green' },
  { problem: '🟨', answer: 'yellow' },
  { problem: '🟡', answer: 'yellow' },
  { problem: '🟪', answer: 'purple' },
  { problem: '🟣', answer: 'purple' },
  { problem: '🟧', answer: 'orange' },
  { problem: '🟠', answer: 'orange' },
  { problem: '🔶', answer: 'orange' },
];

export { letters, specialChars, shortAnimals, bodyParts, colors };
